<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Buildstarted's ramblings</title><link>/</link><description>Buildstarted's ramblings</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m just a lowly programmer.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I live in Southern California with my beautiful wife and a beautiful daughter.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve been programming professionally for about since about 2000 but non-stop since about 1995.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on various things throughout the years. My initial goal was to develop video games. I found
that I&amp;rsquo;m no good at it and was much better at business.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I have a few open source projects. You can find most of them on Github. I currently love developing in
c# and javascript.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There really isn&amp;rsquo;t much more to say just now - I&amp;rsquo;ll flesh this out later :)&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="-buildstarted">-Buildstarted&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>Introducing linksfor.dev(s)</title><link>/post/2020-03-01-linksfor-devs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/2020-03-01-linksfor-devs/</guid><description>&lt;p>For the past year I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a small site called &lt;a href="https://linksfor.dev">linksfor.dev(s)&lt;/a>. Some quick background on why.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I quit social media a few years ago and mostly disappeared from the internet at the same time. The platforms I was on didn&amp;rsquo;t provide the filters
necessary for me to cut out noise and vitriol from my feeds. In order to improve my sanity I simply had to cut myself off.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That&amp;rsquo;s where &lt;a href="https://linksfor.dev">linksfor.dev(s)&lt;/a> came in. It&amp;rsquo;s an automated process that looks at various sources around the internet, vetted by me, gathers
all the links and drops them into a nice interface. Most of the links on the site are automated but occasionally I get a link from a friend
or other source and add them manually.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With the help of the wonderful people on &lt;span title="That migrated to Slack">&lt;code>OG JabbR&lt;/code>&lt;/span> I&amp;rsquo;ve refined the process and added many features
that I think make the service a lot better.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The site is hosted on &lt;a href="https://pages.github.com/">Github Pages&lt;/a> and statically generated using Razor. There are no comments or voting: just pure information.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This site is mainly for me so if you enjoy it then great! If you have any issues you&amp;rsquo;d like to report please post it on the &lt;a href="https://github.com/buildstarted/linksfordevs">issues page&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>New blog, who dis?</title><link>/post/2020-02-26-newblog-who-dis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/2020-02-26-newblog-who-dis/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m back! Sorta. I&amp;rsquo;ll post when I feel like something interests me enough or I want to share
a project I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/archives/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>